Finding Aid for the John Cope Caldwell Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Regnery, Henry, (70); Mar. 11, 1952, Mar. 24, 1952, Apr. 1, 1952, Apr. 25, 1952, Apr. 30, 1952, May 1, 1952, May 16, 1952, May 20, 1952, May 26, 1952, June 2, 1952, Aug. 22, 1952, Sept. 24, 1952, Sept. 25, 1952, Oct. 4, 1952, Oct. 21, 1952, Oct. 23, 1952, Oct. 29, 1952, Nov. 5, 1952, Nov. 28, 1952, Dec. 18, 1952, Dec. 29, 1952, Feb. 26, 1953, Apr. 16, 1953, June 2, 1953, July 20, 1953, Nov. 23, 195: Jan. 7, 1954, June 24, 1954, Aug. 4, 1954, Aug. 10, 1954, Aug. 26, 1954, Sept. 13, 1954, Sept. 23, 1954, Nov. 30, 1954, Dec. 27, 1954, Dec. 30, 1954, Jan. 6, 1955, Jan. 22, 1955, Feb. 17, 1955, Mar. 8, 1955, Mar. 10, 1955, Mar. 16, 1955, Apr. 4, 1955, May 6, 1955, July 17, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Sept. 7, 1956, Oct. 22, 1956, Dec. 6, 1956, Dec. 14, 1956, Jan. 7, 1957, Jan. 28, 1957, Feb. 1, 1957, Mar. 14, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 24, 1957, July 10, 1957, Aug. 9, 1957, Aug. 23, 1957, Dec. 3, 1957, Dec. 11, 1957, Jan. 3, 1958, Oct. 31, 1958, Nov. 12, 1958, Jan. 6, 1959, Jan. 27, 1959, Aug. 31, 1964, Sept. 10, 1964; 7
Reidy, Loretta, (25); June 26, 1951, Aug. 17, 1951, Feb. 19, 1952, Feb. 25, 1952, Aug. 22, 1952, Oct. 7, 1952, Nov. 19, 1952, Dec. 9, 1952, Dec. 17, 1952, Jan. 12, 1953, Jan. 20, 1953, Mar. 25, 1953, Aug. 13, 1953, Jan. 22, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Mar. 3, 1954, Sept. 1, 1954, Oct. 12, 1954, Oct. 15, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954, Apr. 11, 1955, Sept. 26, 1955, Apr. 13, 1956, Dec. 17, 1959, Mar. 10, 1961; 7
Reiff, Julie W., (2); Oct. 31, 1960, Nov. 27, 1960; 7
Reinicke, F. G ., (2); Nov. 20, 1957, Nov. 27, 1957; 8
Ribbe, Walter F ., (1); May 3, 1954; 8
Richards, Jack, (1); Apr. 11, 1955; 8
Richards, Sarra 0., (1); Nov. 25, 1959; 8
Richmond, Brenda, (1); Jan. 19, 1961; 8
Richmond, Charlotte, (10); Mar. 14, 1958, Mar. 31, 1958, Jan. 8, 1959, June 19, 1959, Aug. 21, 1959, Jan. 29, 1960, Aug. 12, Aug. 18, 1960, Sept. 12, 1960, Sept. 14, 1960; 8
Rigby, Patricia, Ann, (1); Feb. 27, 1964; 8
Rikon, Charles, (2); Feb. 13, 1959, Mar. 13, 1959; 8
Riley, C. M ., (1); Nov. 1, 1955; 8
Roberts, Dave, (1); Mar. 26, 1951; 8
Robertson, Anna Douglas, (1); May 20, 1953; 8
Rodes, John B., (1); Mar. 18, 1955; 8
Roerkohl, Marcelline E., (2); Apr. 3, 1963, Jan. 15, 1964; 8
Rogers, George F ., (1); Mar. 12, 1951; 8
Ronnow, Joan, (1); Mar. 11, 1966; 8
Rose, Stuart, (2); Jan. 20, 1954, Jan. 29, 1954; 8
Rosebery, Marguerite T., (1); Mar. 23, 1954; 8
Ross, Michael L., (2); Dec. 29, 1959, Jan. 27, 1960; 8
Ross, Stuart T., (1); Sept. 4, 1962; 8
Rowland, Ronald H ., (1); Jan. 2, 1961; 8
Roy, Leonard C. (1); Nov. 9, 1953; 8
Ruderman, B. H., to Richard J. Walsh, Jr., (1); June 9, 1960; 8
Russell, Dean, (1); Jan. 5, 1955; 8
Russell, Fred, (1); July 8, 1961; 8
Russleape, Mary E., (1); n.d.; 8
Rutowski, Agatha, (7); June 1, 1954, Jan, 18, 1955, Feb. 17, 1955, May 18, 1955, Aug. 19, 1955, Sept. 16, 1955, Oct. 1, 1958; 8
Rutterer, A. J ., (1); Aug. 10, 1959; 8
S
Sabrey, John D., to Lee Keedick, (1); Jan. 27, 1955; 8
Safford, Evelyn, (1); Jan. 18, 1959; 8
Sanders, Charles J ., (1); July 29, 1959; 8
Sanborn, Herbert, (1); Dec. 27, 1955; 8
Sarvola, Reinio, (1); May 6, 1956; 8
Saunders, J. R., (1); Dec. 29, 1953; 8
Saunders, Richard P., (1); May 11, 1956
Saunders, Wilbour E., (1); Jan. 14, 1955; 8
Schell, John, (1); Sept. 1, 1954; 8
Schenk, Elizabeth, (143); Nov. 3, 1950, Nov. 10 1950, Dec. 16, 1950, Dec. 27, 1950, Jan. 16, 1951, Jan. 30, 1951, Feb. 1, 1951, Feb. 20, 1951, Mar. 5, 1951, Mar. 15, 1951, Apr. 9, 1951, June 14, 1951, July 9, 1951, July 17, 1951, Aug. 1, 1951, Aug. 10, 1951, Sept. 4, 1951, Sept. 19, 1951, Sept. 24, 1951, Oct. 3, 1951, Oct. 9, 1951, Oct. 16, 1951, Oct. 19, 1959, Nov. 13, 1951, Dec. 4, 1951, Jan. 8, 1952, Jan. 12, 1952, Feb. 27, 1952, Mar. 28, 1952, May 6, 1952, May 14, 1952, June 3, 1952, June 9, 1952, June 13, 1952, June 20, 1952, July 1, 1952, July 7, 1952, July 8, 1952, July 16, 1952, July 23, 1952, Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 11, 1952, Sept. 12, 1952, Sept. 22, 1952, Oct. 3, 1952, Oct. 15, 1952, Oct. 21, 1952, Nov. 10, 1952, Nov. 14, 1952, Nov. 19, 1952, Dec. 8, 1952, Apr. 25, 1955, Jan. 5, 1953, Jan. 13, 1953, Jan. 30, 1953, Feb. 7, 1953, Mar. 2, 1953, Mar. 24, 1951, Apr. 17, 1953, May 20, 1953, May 25, 1953, June 19, 1953, June 23, 1953, June 26, 1953, July 2, 1953, Sept. 28, 1953, Oct. 2, 1953, Oct. 26, 1953, Dec. 23, 1953, Dec. 28, 1953, Jan. 19, 1954, Mar. 5, 1954, Apr. 1, 1954, May 4, 1954, May 26, 1954, May 28, 1954, June 2, 1954, July 6, 1954, July 13, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 16, 1954, Aug. 31, 1954, Sept. 16, 1954, Nov. 24, 1943, Dec. 1, 1954, Dec. 28, 1954, Dec. 31, 1954, Jan. 13, 1955, Jan. 14, 1955, Feb. 21, 1955, Mar. 8, 1955, May 19, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955, Sept. 7, 1955, Oct. 17, 1955, Oct. 27, 1955, Nov. 8, 1955, Nov. 22, 1955, Dec. 2, 1955, Feb. 17, 1956, Mar. 23, 1956, Apr. 26, 1956, Oct. 24, 1956, June 1, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956, Sept. 4, 1956, Sept. 14, 1956, Nov, 27, 1956, Dec. 3, 1956, Dec. 13, 1956, Dec. 17, 1956, Jan. 5, 1957, Jan. 23, 1957, Feb. 15, 1957, Feb. 18, 1957, Apr. 1, 1957, June 6, 1957, June 14, 1957, July 30, 1957, Aug. 20, 1957, Nov. 9, 1957, Dec. 18, 1957, Feb. 13, 1958, Oct. 23, 1958, Nov. 22, 1958, Feb. 18, 1959, Mar. 12, 1959, Apr. 7, 1959, May 19, 1959, June 11, 1959, June 15, 1959, Sept.22, 1959, Oct. 14, 1959, Oct. 20, 1959, Nov. 20, 1959, Mar. 30, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept 29, 1960, Nov. 11, 1960, Nov. 18, 1960, Dec. 19, 1960, n.d.; 8
Schmidt, Charles, (1); n.d.; 8
Schultz, Connie J ., (1); Jan. 12, 1961; 8
Schultz, Russell H., (1); Apr. 27, 1963; 8
Scott, Glenn, ( 1), Jan. 15, 1953; 8
Scott, Otho E., (1); Feb. 19, 1957; 8
Shackford, R. H., (1); Feb. 2, 1957; 8
Shai, Lai, (1); Sept. 28, 1956; 8
Shain, Charles J., (4); Apr. 2, 1955, Apr. 21, 1955, May 30, 1955, n.d.; 8
Shan, Trevor R., (1); Oct. 23, 1957; 8
Shea, William, (1); Sept. 16, 1955; 8
Shemanski, Frances, (2); Jan. 12, 1961, Jan. 2, 1962; 8
Shen, Samson C., (7); Feb. 27, 1956, Apr. 2, 1956, Apr. 28, 1956, Aug. 24, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Dec. 4, 1956, Apr. 4, 1958; 8
Shen, T. H., to C. C. Shao, (1); n.d.; 8
Sherako, Lorraine, (1); Dec. 8, 1959; 8
Shideler, Jack, (2); July 2, 1959, Oct. 12, 1959; 8
Shih, Hu, to Magnus I. Gregerson, (1); Mar. 16, 1956; 8
Shin, Nichol, (2); Nov. 26, 1954, Jan. 13, 1955; 8
Shi Tae, Kim, (1); Oct. 20, 1954; 8
Shoemaker, Evelyn, (1); March 25, 1956; 8
Shouse, Len, to Lee Keedick, (1); Dec. 27, 1954; 8
Shriver, Thomas A., (1); Oct. 6, 1950; 8
Shu, F. M. S., (2); Dec. 22, 1956, Jan. 28, 1957; 8
Simester, Ralph E., (1); Nov. 8, 1952; 8
Simmonds, Niva, (2); Nov. 4, 1959, n.d.; 8
Sinclair, John T ., (3); Feb. 24, 1953, Aug. 11, 1964, n.d.; 8
Sindelar, J. C. (6); July 28, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954, Sept. 2, 1954, Sept. 14, 1954, Oct. 6, 1954, Oct. 20, 1954; 8
Skinner, Clara, (3); Mar. 23, 1956, Aug, 6, 1956, Mar. 29, 1966; 8
Skinner, L. E., (2); Jan. 17, 1957, Dec. 26, 1957; 8
Skinner, Marguerite, (1); n.d.; 8
Sloane, Rubert D., (1); June 11, 1962; 8
Smart, Alberto, (1); Jan. 20, 1961; 8
Smith, Anne E. (1); Feb. 17, 1954; 8
Smith, Beatrice M., (1); May 14, 1953; 8
Smith, C. R., (1); Dec. 29, 1953; 8
Smith, Carolyn S., (1); n.d.; 8
Smith, Frank L., (1); Jan. 13, 1959; 8
Smith, Guy, L., (1); Oct. 6, 1952; 8
Smith, Henry W., (1); Jan. 29, 1958; 8
Smith, Paul C,, to Robert Keedick, (1); June 23, 1955; 8
Smith, Winfred R., (1); n.d.; 8
Sneider, Vern, (1); Feb. 18, 1955; 8
Snell, Lottie, (2); Feb. 20, 1958; 8
Snell, Ray, (3); Dec. 16, 1952, Aug. 5, 1953, Nov. 24, 1953; 8
Soenksen, Rodney M., (1); Feb. 26, 1960; 8
Solt, Guy, W., to H, W. Luhnow, (1); Feb. 20, 1953; 8
Soto, Teresa, (1); June 27, 1955; 8
Souder, M. Attie, (2); Oct. 16, 1958, Nov. 9, 1958; 8
Southgate, Herbert S., (3); July 15, 1953, Jan. 29, 1954, Sept. 4, 1954; 8
Sowell, F. C ., (1); June 20, 1951; 8
Spadea Columns, Inc., (16); Sept. 30, 1957, May 26, 1958, Oct. 29, 1958, Nov. 28, 1958, Feb. 2, 1959, Mar. 4, 1959, Apr. 3, 1959, May 8, 1959, July 8, 1959, Sept. 11, 1959, Oct. 30, 1959, June 20, 1960, Sept. 28, 1960, Nov. 14, 1960, n.d., n.d.; 8
Spadea, James V., to Frank Dorn and Bill Reiche, (2); July 29, 1953, Oct. 15, 1953; 8
Spadea, James V., (44); July 21, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Aug. 10, 1953, Oct. 8, 1953, Oct. 19, 1953, Nov. 6, 1953, Nov. 9, 1953, Nov. 10, 1953, Nov. 10, 1953, Nov. 13, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953, Dec. 2, 1953, Jan. 5, 1954, Jan. 6, 1954, Jan. 27, 1954, Jan. 28, 1954, Mar. 2, 1954, Mar. 9, 1954, June 24, 1954, July 30, 1954, Sept. 16, 1954, Oct. 1, 1954, Oct. 5, 1954, Dec. 1, 1954, Dec. 30, 1954, Jan. 19, 1955, Apr. 11, 1955, June 22, 1955, Setp. 29, 1955, Oct. 4, 1955, Dec. 8, 1955, Jan. 4, 1956, Jan. 19, 1956, Feb. 20, 1956, Feb. 20, 1956, Aug. 1, 1956, Oct. 23, 1956, Nov. 27, 1956, Apr. 10, 1958, Jan. 16, 1959, Oct. 12, 1960, n.d., n.d.; 8
Spadea, Stirling, (10); Nov. 9, 1953, Nov. 16, 1953, May 24, 1954, Dec. 7, 1956, Jan. 4, 1957, May 20, 1957, July 18, 1957, Aug. 26, 1957, Aug. 26, 1958, May 1, 1959; 8
Sparks, Fred, (1); Mar. 20, 1955; 8
Speer, Robert P., (1); Aug. 5, 1955; 8
Speers, Theodore C., (1); Mar. 9, 1951; 8
Spencer, George A. P., to E. Bigwood, (1); Sept. 14, 1960; 8
Spender, Percy, to U. G. Murphy, (1); Jan. 4, 1957; 8
Spottswood, C. L., (1); Mar. 23, 1956; 8
Stahlman, James G., (1); Aug. 27, 1951; 8
Stanley, H. F., (4); June 24, 1959, July 9, 1959, Sept. 28, 1959, Oct. 12, 1959; 8
Starbuck, Philip N., (4); Aug. 22, 1951, Sept. 7, 1951, Aug. 27, 1952, Sept. 5, 1952; 8
Starr, C. C ., (2); Mar. 15, 1957, n.d.; 8
Steeves, John M., (1); Dec. 28, 1965; 8
Steiner, Anthony, (1); Apr. 26, 1963; 8
Sterling, Phyllis M., (1); Oct. 24, 1952; 8
Stewart, James L. (2); Oct. 28, 1948, Oct. 5, 1956; 8
Stewart, Shan, (6); Aug. 7, 1959, Feb. 18, 1960, Sept. 8, 1962, Oct. 3, 1962, Oct. 13, 1962, n.d.; 8
Steyn, Mary T., to William J. Dowling and Mildred D. Glass, (2); Jan. 24, 1957, Mar. 18, 1957; 8
Stokeman, Christina, (1); Oct. 29, 1953; 8
Stand, Eleanor, (2); Apr. 30, 1953, May 23, 1953; 8
Straus, Roger W ., (2); July 13, 1955, July 19, 1955; 8
Straus, Ernest, (5); July 29, 1952, June 8, 1953, June 9, 1953, Mar. 8, 1955, n.d.; 8
Straus, Filicia B., (1); Dec. 2, 1953; 8
Strube, William F., to Charles Elder, Stewart Kritsky, Bernie Schweid, Bruce Mills, Howard Clarke, and Henry Regnery, (6); Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug 19, 1952, Oct. 7, 1954, Dec. 8, 1954, June 29, 1955; 8
Strube, William F., (30); May 8, 1952, May 14, 1952, May 19, 1952, June 16, 1952, June 25, 1952, Aug. 7, 1952, Aug. 19, 1952, Aug 25, 1952, Sept. 2, 1952, Sept. 9, 1952, Sept. 19, 1952, Sept. 24, 1952, Oct. 3, 1952, Oct. 7, 1952, Dec. 8, 1952, Jan. 9, 1953, Apr. 22, 1953, June 10, 1953, June 11, 1953, June 17, 1953, Jan. 28, 1954, Sept. 10, 1954, Nov. 4, 1954, Feb. 14, 1955, Feb. 18, 1955, Mar. 7, 1955, June 30, 1955, Sept. 23, 1959, n.d., n.d.; 8
Stryker, Lisie B., (1); Mar. 11, 1959; 8
Stuntz, Hugh C.. (1); Sept. 19, 1952; 8
Stutts, Barbara L., (1); n.d.; 8
Suh, Eton, (8); Nov. 17, 1950, Mar. 26, 1951, Apr. 3, 1951, Sept. 19, 1951, June 12, 1952, Nov. 20, 1953, Aug. 4, 1954, Aug. 29, 1954; 8
Summers, Joe A., (1); Sept. 4, 1951; 8
Sun, Lew Ho, (1); June 20, 1952; 8
Sutherland, Kirk E., to Lee Keedick, (1); July 13, 1951; 8
Swanson, Helen R., (1); Jan. 7, 1954; 8
T
Tanner, E. S., (1); Sept. 6, 1952; 9
Tao, Frank (4); Aug. 29, 1955, Jan. 6, 1959, July 30, 1959, Nov. 28, 1959; 9
Tate, Velma N ., (4); May 22, 1957, Aug. 16, 1957, Sept. 16, 1957, June 3, 1958; 9
Tanabe, Shinichi, (1); Dec. 26, 1957; 9
Tay, Paul, (5); Dec. 4*1956, Mar. 20, 1959, May 18, 1959, May 28, 1959, Aug. 22, 1959; 9
Tayl, Jim, (1); Sept. 23, 1957; 9
Teetor, Paul, (2); Mar. 14, 1951, May 18, 1951; 9
Templeton, Payne, (1); Dec. 28, 1956; 9
Tenske, Marcia, (1); n.d.; 9
Thacher, Liz, (1); Mar. 19, 1951; 9
Thaller, Victor C., (1); June 7, 1961; 9
Theoblad, Jack W ., (1); June 1, 1955; 9
Thompson, Curtis C., to Mituko, (3); June 13, 1950, Sept. 26, 1950, Nov, 22, 1950; 9
Thompson, Naomi, (1); Jan. 29, 1957; 9
Thompson, P. W ., (1); Nov. 24, 1958; 9
Thompson, Jill, (1); Nov. 30, 1964; 9
Thompson, Marcelline E., (1); Feb. 10, 1966; 9
Thomson, Robert P., (1); June 14, 1957; 9
Thurman, Pauline, (1); Mar. 5, 1962; 9
Tiffany, Helen, (1); Feb. 19, 1955; 9
Todd, Jo Ann, (1); May 26, 1960; 9
Tomkins, Ellsworth, to Richard Walsh, (1); Jan. 5, 1956; 9
Tomkins, Ellsworth, (1); Dec. 6, 1955; 9
Tones, V. E., (1); Sept. 28, 1957; 9
Tong, H. K., (3); May 28, 1956, May 29, 1956, Feb. 6, 1958; 9
Tower, Howard E., (1); Apr. 20, 1959; 9
Tracy, Crete C., (2); Feb. 1, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957; 9
Tracey, Jean, (1); Feb. 8, 1955; 9
Treadwell, James H. W ., (2); Sept. 22, 1962, Oct. 17, 1962; 9
Traum, William R ., (2)); Mar. 22, 1952, Nov. 26, 1952; 9
Truitt, Patricia, (1); July 30, 1957; 9
Tseng, George, (1); Jan. 12, 1958; 9
Tsiang, Tingfu F., (2); Nov. 24, 1954, Feb. 23, 1955; 9
Tuerk, Gladys R., (1); Jan. 13, 1959; 9
Tull, James N ., (1); May 29, 1956; 9
Tunney, Gene, (1); Dec. 11, 1956; 9
Turnbull, Ruth W ., (1); July 13, 1955; 9
Turner, George, to Deryck Aluvihare, S. N. Chib, M. B. K. Malik, and Sri Budojo, (4); Sept. 28, 1959; 9
Turner, George, (2); May 22, 1958, Mar. 11, 1959; 9
Turner, Lucille C., (1); Nov. 18, 1958; 9
Turner, William D., (1); Jan. 14, 1955; 9
Tyler, Lee, (3); Apr. 1, 1959, Aug. 11, 1959, Aug. 26, 1959; 9
U
Ulrich, Jolton, to Dr. Poling, (1); n.d.; 9
Underwood, G ., (1); May 25, 1962; 9
Ushida, Hirozo, (2); Oct. 7, 1959, Jan. 28, 1960; 9
Utley, William T., (1); Nov. 11, 1959; 9
V
Vander Meer, Alma, (1); Sept. 4, 1956; 9
Vance, R. R., to R. H. Porter, (1); n.d.; 9
Vance, R. R., (1); Aug. 31, 1955; 9
Vandas, Edna, (1); July 10, 1953; 9
Van Ness, Catherine L., (1); Feb. 10, 1958; 9
Vaurs, Roger, (1); Jan. 22, 1958; 9
Veigel, Ernest W ., (1); May 5, 1959; 9
Viteri, Luis, (1); Mar. 7, 1961; 9
Vogel, Frank J ., (2); Apr. 5, 1960, Apr. 18, 1960; 9
Vogt, Gertrude E., (2); May 5, 1954, May 13, 1954; 9
Voorhess, Lacy, (1); n.d.; 9
W
Waldhorn, Valerie, to Barbara Beggi, (1); July 8, 1963; 9
Waldhorn, Valerie, (2); June 17, 1963, Aug. 3, 1965; 9
Waldorf, Howard, (3); Feb. 8, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, June
Walker, Richard., (1); Feb. 6, 1959; 9
Wallace, DeWitt, to Lim Rei Cheng, (1); May 19, 1958; 9
Wallace, DeWitt, (5); July 18, 1956, Sept. 10, 1956, Nov. 20, 1956, July 15, 1957; 9
Wallace, G. D., to H. Johnson, (1); July 9, 1963; 9
Wallin, Katherine, to Robert Keedick, (1); Nov. 13, 1957; 9
Walsh, Agatha, to Richard J. Walsh, Jr., (1); July 1, 1959; 9
Walsh, Mary 0. L., (93); Nov. 11, 1957, Mar. 21, 1958, Mar. 26, 1958, June 3, 1958, Aug. 6, 1958, Aug. 15, 1958, Aug. 27, 1958, Feb.3, 1959, Feb. 11, 1959, Feb. 18, 1959, Feb. 18, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, Mar. 6, 1959, Apr. 7, 1959, Apr. 29, 1959, July 21, 1959, Oct. 2, 1959, Dec. 10, 1959, Jan. 29, 1960, Jan. 22, 1960, Mar. 29, 1960, Apr. 28, 1960, May 4, 1960, May 18, 1960, June 8, 1960, June 14, 1960, June 30, 1960, July 18, 1960, July 19, 1960, Aug. 3, 1960, Aug. 4, 1960, Aug. 18, v 1960, Sept. 12, 1960, Sept. 14, 1960, Nov. 2, 1960, Jan. 9. 1961, Jan. 24, 1961, Mar. 23, 1961, Apr. 5, 1961, Apr. 14, 1961, Apr.. 14, 1961, Apr. 24, 1961, Sept. 11, 1961, Sept. 26, 1961, Oct. 27, 1961, Nov. 3, 1961, Nov. 8, 1961, Nov. 17, 1961, Dec. 28.,' 1961, Jan. 8, 1962, Mar. 13, 1962, Apr. 25, 1962, Sept. 10, 1962, Oct. 18, 1962, Dec. 6, 1962, Jan. 3, 1963, Jan. 22, 1963, Jan. 29, 1963, Feb. 6, 1963, Feb. 7, 1963, Feb. 13, 1962, May 10, 1963, May 21, 1963, June 10, 1963, June 26, 1963, July 3, 1963, July 10, 1963, Aug. 2, 1963, Aug. 15, 1963, Aug. 27, 1963, Aug. 27, 1963, Oct. 2, 1963, Nov. 6, 1963, Nov. 13, 1963, Nov. 14, 1963, Nov. 27, 1963, Dec. 11, 1963, Dec. 12, 1963, Apr. 29, 1964, May 14, 1964, June 26, 1964, July 16, 1964, July 29, 1964, Sept. 3, 1964, Sept. 11, 1964, Oct. 21, 1964, Nov. 11, 1964, Dec. 11, 1964, May 22, 1965, Sept. 14, 1965, Spet. 22, 1965, Oct. 26, 1965, Oct. 26, 1965; 9
Walsh, Richard J. to Daniel A. Poling, John F. Cronin, Dave Schaffnit, J. Calvitt Clarke, Marvin Liebman, Raymond E. Fideler, Robert T. Oliver, I. Yokota, Peter Hiatt, Virginia Kirkus, Norman E., Koehler, Shirley Fockler, Robert Arculli, and Richard R. Saunders, (15); Nov. 25, 1955, Jan. 6, 1956, July 30, 1956, Aug. 30, 1956, Jan. 29, 1957, Jan. 8, 1959, Feb. 24, 1959, Mar. 17, 1959, July 31, 1959, Sept. 3, 1959, May 26, 1960, Nov. 9, 1960, June 23, 1960, Dec. 21, 1960, May 12, 1961; 9
Walsh, Richard J., (396); Apr. 22, 1955, May 13, 1955, May 26, 1955, June 1, 1955, June 15, 1955, July 8, 1955, July 13, 1955, July 14, 1955, July 20, 1955, July 20, 1955, Aug. 16, 1955, Aug. 23, 1955, Aug. 26, 1955, Sept. 8, 1955, Sept. 20, 1955, Oct. 7, 1955, Oct. 11, 1955, Oct. 12, 1955, Oct. 12, 1955, Oct. 27, 1955, Oct. 31, 1955, Nov. 15, 1955, Nov. 17, 1955, Dec. 5, 1955, Jan. 6, 1956, Jan. 20, 1956, Feb. 6, 1956, Feb. 21, 1956, Mar. 2, 1956, Mar. 7, 1956, Mar. 8, 1956, Mar. 22, 1956, Mar. 27, 1956, Apr. 4, 1956, Apr. 12, 1956, Apr. 18, 1956, Apr. 26, 1956, May 21, 1956, May 28, 1956, June 1, 1956, June 22, 1956, July 2, 1956, July 18, 1956, Aug. 3, 1956 July 30, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Aug. 16, 1956, Aug. 21, 1956, Aug. 27, 1956, Aug. 27, 1956, Sept. 12, 1956, Oct. 2, 1956, Oct. 4, 1956, Oct. 9, 1956, Oct. 15, 1956, Oct. 22, 1956, Oct. 29, 1956, Nov. 13, 1956, Nov. 15, 1956, Nov. 21, 1956, Nov. 27, 1956, Dee. 5, 1956, Dee. 7, 1956, Dee. 14, 1956, Dee. 21, 1956, Dee. 28, 1956, Jan. 9, 1957, Jan. 23, 1957, Jan. 29, 1957, Feb. 1, 1957, Feb. 11, 1957, Feb. 14, 1957, Mar. 8, 1957, Mar. 14, 1957, Mar. 22, 1957, Mar. 27, 1957, Apr. 2, 1957, Apr. 5, 1957, Apr. 12, 1957, Apr, 24, 1957, Apr. 29, 1957, May 3, 1957, May 10, 1957, May 14, 1957, May 28, 1957, June 24, 1957, August 22, 1957, Oct. 18, 1957, Nov. 8, 1957, Nov. 11, 1957, Nov. 13, 1957, Nov. 15, 1957, Nov. 22, 1957, Nov. 26, 1957, Dee. 5, 1957, Dee. 13, 1957, Dee. 18, 1957, Feb. 10, 1958, Feb. 20, 1958, Feb. 25, 1958, Mar. 13, 1958, Apr. 7, 1958, Apr. 14, 1958, Apr. 16, 1958, Apr. 17, 1958, May 8, 1958, May 19, 1958, May 21, 1958, June 20, 1958, June 27, 1958, July 21, 1958, July 30, 1958, Aug. 26, 1958, Sept. 11, 1958, Sept. 23, 1958, Oct. 23, 1958, Oct. 27, 1958, Nov. 5, 1958, Nov. 10, 1958, Nov. 11, 1958, Nov. 18, 1958,- Nov. 18, 1958, Nov. 20, 1958, Nov. 21, 1958, Dee. 3, 1958, Dee. 5, 1958, Dee. 8, 1958, Dee. 18, 1958, Dee. 30, 1958, Jan. 9, 1959, Jan. 12, 1959, Jan. 16, 1959, Jan. 22, 1959, Feb. 10, 1959, Feb. 16, 1959, Feb. 17, 1959, Feb. 20, 1959, Feb. 27, 1959, Mar. 10, 1959, Mar. 11, 1959, Mar. 20, 1959, Mar. 20, 1959, Mar. 26, 1959, Mar. 27, 1959, Apr. 2, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 14, 1959, Apr. 21, 1959, Apr. 29, 1959, May 4, 1959, May 14, 1959, May 18, 1959, May 25, 1959, June 1, 1959, June 16, 1959, June 19, 1959, June 24, 1959, July 15, 1959, July 20, 1959, July 21, 1959, July 24, 1959, July 30, 1959, Aug. 4, 1959, Aug. 18,1959 Aug. 24, 1959, Aug. 28, 1959, Sept. 3, 1959, Sept. 22, 1959, Sept. 28, 1959, Sept. 30, 1959, Oct. 5, 1959, Oct. 9, 1959, Oct. 14, 1959, Oct. 21, 1959, Nov. 10, 1959, Oct. 26, 1959, Oct. 29, 1959, Nov. 17, 1959, Nov. 23, 1959, Dee. 7, 1959, Dee. 29, 1959, Jan. 22, 1960, Jan. 25, 1960, Feb. 2, I960, Feb. 4, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 16, 1960, Feb. 19, 1960, Feb. 24, 1960, Feb. 26, 1960, Mar. 3, 1960, Mar. 8, 1960, Mar. 8, 1960, Mar. 10, 1960, Mar. 21, 1960, Mar. 24, 1960, Apr. 1, 1960, Apr. 20, 1960, Apr. 21, 1960, May 4, 1960; 9 May 4, 1960, May 12, 1960, May 24, 1960, June 10, 1960, June 13, 1960, June 15, 1960, June 27, 1960, June 29, 1960, June 29, 1960, June 29, 1960, July 8, 1960, July 12, 1960, July 12, 1960, July 18, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 20, 1960, July 26, 1960, July 27, 1960, July 29, 1960, Aug. 11, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960, Aug. 12, 1960, Aug. 15, 1960, Aug. 17, 1960, Aug. 18, 1960, Aug. 23, 1960, Aug. 24, 1960, Aug. 24, 1960, Aug. 30, 1960, Sept. 6, 1960, Sept. 8, 1960, Sept. 13, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 1, 1960, Nov. 9, 1960, Nov. 10, 1960, Nov. 15, 1960, Nov. 16, 1960, Dec. 5, 1960, Dec. 9, 1960, Jan. 3, 1951, Jan. 5, 1961, Jan. 13, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 17, 1961, Jan. 30 1961, Feb. 10, 1961, Feb. 15, 1961, Feb. 17, 1961, Feb. 23, 1961, Feb. 23, 1961, Feb. 24, 1961, Mar. 2, 1961, Mar. 8, 1961, Mar. 27, 1961, Apr. 3, 1961, Apr. 10, 1961, Apr. 11, 1961, Apr. 19, 1961, Apr. 21, 1961, Apr. 26, 1961, Apr. 26, 1961, May.8, 1961, May 31, 1961, June 2, 1961, June 8, 1961, June 8, 1961, June 20, 1961, June 20, 1961, June 23, 1961, June 30, 1961, July 12, 1961, July 25, 1961, July 25, 1961, Aug. I, 1961, Aug. 11, 1961, Aug. 24, 1961, Sept. 8, 1961, Sept. 13, 1961, Sept. 14, 1961, Sept. 29, 1961, Sept. 29, 1961, Oct. 3, 1961, Oct. 6, 1961, Oct. 23, 1961, Dec. 1, 1961, Dec. 4, 1961, Dec. 11, 1961, Dec. 13, 1961, Dec. 28, 1961, Jan. 3, 1962, Jan. 5, 1962, Jan. II, 1962, Jan. 15, 1962, Jan. 17, 1962, Jan. 19, 1962, Jan. 23, 1962, Feb. 5, 1962, Feb. 16, 1962, Feb. 21, 1962, Feb. 28, 1962, Apr. 30, 1962, May 2, 1962, June 20, 1962, June 22, 1962, Aug. 27, 1962, Sept. 27, 1962, Oct. 12, 1962, Nov. 9, 1962, Nov. 13, 1962, Nov. 27, 1962, Dec. 3, 1962, Jan. 2, 1963, Jan. 3, 1963, Jan. 25, 1963, Feb. 12, 1963, Feb. 15-, 1963, Feb. 19, 1963, Feb. 19, 1963, Mar. 1, 1963, Mär. 5, 1963, Mar. 19, 1963, May 10, 1963, June 5, 1963, June 10, 1963, June 17, 1963, July 3, 1963, Aug. 5, 1963, Sept. 3, 1963, Sept. 6, 1963, Sept. 10, 1963, Oct. 1, 1963, Oct. 14, 1963, Oct. 25, 1963, Dec. 4, 1963, Dec. 12, 1963, Dec. 19, 1963, Dec. 24, 1963, Jan. 6, 1964, Feb. 10, 1964, Mar. 18., 1964, Mar. 27, 1964, Apr. 13, 1964, June 3, 1964, July 8, 1964, July 8, 1964, Aug. 25, 1964, Sept. 9, 1964, Sept. 23, 1964, Oct. 6, 1964, Oct. 9, 1964, Dec. 30, 1964, Feb. 3, 1965, Feb. 12, 1965, Feb. 20, 1965, Mar. 5, 1965, Apr, 6, 1965, Apr. 27, 1965, May 6, 1965, May 14, 1965, June 11, 1965, June 18, 1965, June 30, 1965, July 13, 1965, July 19, 1965, July 22, 1965, July 23, 1965, July 27, 1965, Aug. 3, 1965, Aug. 6, 1965, Aug. 9, 1965, Aug. 18, 1965, Aug. 24, 1965, Aug. 27, 1965, Aug. 27, 1965, Sept. 14, 1965, Sept. 16. 1965, Sept. 21, 1965, Oct. 28, 1965, Nov. 2, 1965, Nov. 19, 1965, Nov. 22, 1965, Nov. 29, 1965, Dec. 6, 1965, Dec. 9, 1965, Dec. 10, 1965, Dec. 14, 1965, n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d., n.d.; 10
Walter, Francis E., (1); June 28, 1956; 10
Ward, Hiley H., (25); Feb. 7, 1956, Feb. 15, 1956, Feb. 22, 1956, Feb. 28, 1956, Mar. 5, 1956, Mar. 15, 1956, Mar. 21, 1956, Mar. 29, 1956, Apr. 12, 1956, Apr. 19, 1956, May 4, 1956, May 28, 1956, May 31, 1956, June 4, 1956, June 6, 1956, July 2, 1956, July 30, 1956, Aug. 9, 1956, Aug. 15, 1956, Sept. 21, 1956, Nov. 1, 1956, Nov. 15, 1956, Dec. 11, 1956, Nov. 4, 1957, Apr. 10, 1958; 10
Warfield, Charles H. (1); Feb. 18, 1954; 10
Washko, Michael, (1); Dec. 19, 1957; 10
Watson, Tom, (4); June 28, 1953, Aug. 3, 1953, Nov. 23, 1953, n.d.; 10
Wayman, Paul L, to Mr. Holladay, (1); Sept. 5, 1960; 10
Webb, Elaine, (1); n.d.; 10
Weems, Clarence N ., (1); Oct. 26. 1952; 10
Wei, C. C., (3); Feb. 19, 1957, Feb. 19, 1958, Apr. 16, 1958; 10
Whalen, Richard, (1); Aug. 12, 1956; 10
Wheatley, Ralph, (1); June 25, 1954; 10
Wheeler, W. L ., (1); June 16, 1953; 10
White, Robert L ., (2); July 30, 1958, n.d.; 10
White, Sue T ., (5); Nov. 26, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958, Dec. 13, 1959, Aug. 20, 1960, n.d.; 10
White, William L., to Alfred S. Dasheil, (1); Aug. 9, 1954; 10
White, William L ., (11); Mar. 4, 1954, June 24, 1954, Aug. 5, 1954, Aug. 6, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 9, 1954, Aug. 12, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954, Oct. 6, 1954, Feb. 2, 1955, n.d.; 10
Whitla, J. M ., (1); Dec. 28, 1964; 10
Whitman, E. S., to Alice Widener, (1); Dec. 10, 1956; 10
Whitted, G. W., to Richard J. Walsh, (1); July 2, 1959; 10
Widener, Alice, (20); Mar. 21, 1955, Mar. 31, 1955 June 5, 1955, June 30, 1955, June 30, 1955, July 13, 1955, July 18, 1955, Feb. 22, 1956, Mar. 8, 1956, Apr. 3, 1956, May 31, 1956, June 15, 1956, July 20, 1956, July 27, 1956, Dec. 17, 1956, Jan. 3, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957, Apr. 10, 1958, n.d.; 10
Wieck, Fred, to Ruth M. Elmquist, (1); June 8, 1953; 10